Hi Okay next
ajnabi The Forgotten Sands
image Globalindo scholars the
same method has been chili-cabaian menow
www.sd which is split
sachsen
agenbni46 ostrich Swings debut
talks about god that is make
so strong in the last line he is so
generous do not go to study Dharma
do not understand about emptiness
but because they are so generous
or attached born best as
real beings born as
powerful beings and
remain
Aya Ray then he also so citizens
speak if it comes from his
own Side then they cannot change
and this is this inspiration also not
us
who are now is an idea that we can be
closed and intend after we
die
or if we come to
your wish list without and very
and if we can
where we come from confused students
if we can remember with
past life
then we will be
Hi good people all there
will be no information International
conflict
remembering
from in my opinion sometimes when
we are really studying
[Music]
we do not ask the
most effective question which is why we
can not see our past life
people we choose past life and
why do not we
remember
Why is it the same  once I don't
miss life too much I
So I have something about whether
you're a
thing you can hear me now
member sign
ws
my brother's person just had Hi
really
Dad has a feeling that it's definitely in my
past life I wasn't a
little Oki my cooking was very bad
but I don't remember in the past
Korea is Who
told this story
shark expert and shave indeed if you
feel
if you feel you should
remember it
or I should be able to remember
my past life then you don't
understand where you come from Okay you
still have a feeling that there is me
who has my
past life my past thoughts
addresses this weschool there is a school
about the middle way B believe the
they believe that Michael
giveaway military basic
is my consciousness the
person who is listening to
my thoughts is Michael and that feels
right Yes wes Neng I listen
I have a body Okay
but I'm not from me
gecella is not her finger gecella but
gecella has fingers so there is gecella
and Gisella has fingers but
gecella is not these fingers
so
westfield G after definitely some kind of
spirit so
freely
and the spirit
moves from one life to the
next but the spirit is Geisha
Michael  she
left this body we can
see it
we can see quesella's body
left in this world then
buried
software review we feel like
there must be a real gecella who
continues the next life
and also Islam left this body
then he went to another world
we don't know what happens in the
mind with our mind will also
this mind can't be seen we can
feel that there are other people's thoughts
we can see it from their gaze or
from their smiles come on
how they frown we can
conclude that this person has
thoughts through their facial expressions
and through what they say from
what they do but you
can't see
What is the mind Joshua March Falling
behind So if gecella left
her body Maybe she took her mind
with her body is here
but gecella
ismika vegas.win maybe gecella is
Hip her mind gecella
maybe this gecella's mind continues the
next life
then gecella will bring or enter the
next body and that's how
we've been thinking about
rebirth Keyla is in
this body then this body gets old
then
gecella gets out of this car then
Desa gets into another car and
gesselchaft continues to drive this car well that's how
install Kidul  sincere
event talking panchen lama
a like when we move on to the
next life it feels like
we change cars we get out of the
old car into a new car and then we
continue to move on to the next life
still driving but what
he actually said is actually no
one gets into the old car or the
new car it's not you and not yourself
You also
leave your mind when you
get out of the old car yeah Okay Novi
your body has been left behind
But your mind is also left behind
Yulia and you leave Michael
Telo bodyshop slides Pattinson
I know that sometimes
Buddhism talks as if it's
talking like this but actually
it's not true because it's
just a matter of language so it's not
true that Polri loader Ah usually lakel
gets out of one body
then gets into a new body
that's not true because
if it's like that then
some people should be able to remember
their old car right Wait a minute I want to
turn off this soup cooker
Hi
b**** my
old migme gave me a nickname
30 years ago he gave me the name of the
burnt cook because I always
burn all the dishes
and praise the burning trail as all the pots
So it's not Jessie Michael gets out of
one body moves into another body So
This is how the
new seeds are open,
Michael is the one who just opened so
I'm not the one who changed cars
from one life to the
next, currently the seeds are open
as gecella in
gecella's thoughts and gecella's body, then the
seeds, the seeds, the
gecella's thoughts stop,
gecella's body stops, then the
new seeds open
10 minutes after I died, the
new seeds open, there are no more
gecellas
present at that time, only
new seeds open at that time, many
are completely new people.
Of course, he can't remember his
past life because of
oxygen because now, all of
it is new seeds that open
so he can't remember this is
just a new body, new thoughts.
Hello friends, it's not gecella coming out of his
old body like his old body
is an old car and getting into a
new car or a new body,
close the maintenance, so move the
old one,
this is the old gecella seeds, the
old gecella thoughts are finished now
in the new Beat that opens and he
will be a completely
different person, so of course he won't
remember his past life because
this is a different person,
different thoughts, I know,
right?  We don't usually talk
like this but the purpose of this poem is
very interesting
Dad likes to tell
my students how long it took
for
Michael to become a dog
How long does it take Is
it true that
screen geisler went to the
spirit world for seven weeks
then if he was lucky he chose a
new car a new body Oh no
that's true because seeds open
65 seeds per second
so
how long does it take
to get into a new car and to
get into a new mind and
into a new person's body it
only takes one sixty-fifth of a second
I don't know why we feel
safe everyday if we have nothing left the second we
die then we say it's okay
we have seven weeks to
think about it people will pray for
me gecella will pray for me
so it's not an emergency right I
have seven weeks to choose
good seeds for
my next life but it's not like that
actually it
doesn't take hours to become
a dog you don't have to wait for a
dog's body to develop it's not like
that it only takes one sixty-fifth of a
second your whole body
your whole mind can change into
another creature YouTube less than
a second don't think about it Oh I
have seven to prepare myself
don't worry Again Sheila I have
seven weeks to  find the
next body that is more comfortable no it's not
like that what seeds you have
When you die that
will determine what you will be
next It's not even your choice what
you want to be only what seeds you
have in your mind when
you die that will
make your next life
you can't choose if your seeds are
good then your next life will be
very good happy But
when there are bad seeds then it will
cause bad things for
people too Next this so if part
of part of you comes
from yourself
sexual kwarda then we can say Oh
quesella is in another realm let's
pray that she can get into the next body
but that's not it
when you die
you leave your car you
leave yourself
and you have a new car new body new
thoughts new self
Let's follow this text
I'm afraid we won't finish
this Even in 100 years He
said
the New Humans super beings
or Gods
you have to imagine only
this is a possibility for the future Van
you know there's a children's game
called marbles that are round modem
Danda is made of glass
the children's game is a god
they play with planets like
they play with marbles it's
not only Iron Man who can do that
when they are having fun
tweeting they can play with the
planet they can throw Mars just like that
they are very powerful and
very powerful but
they also have one problem
they feel that this ballpoint pen is made
in Japan and they bought it from
Japan they still think like that
they have good seeds that are
open
they have the power to play
with the planet like it is just a
ball but they still don't understand
why
fortune and they also don't know that
it is the result of the seeds that are open
from their lives other than before
Okay B violet
so
Store
How can someone form an
attachment to
something
we can talk MP3
for a long time about
how good things also happen in
your life or bad things happen
help
but in short you can't
point to a
point where Pok ballpoint pen Ain Hai
started
can't say Oh November
10th came out of the factory this ballpoint pen but
when is the exact time when he
became a pen you can't
find the duck or the moment that the ballpoint pen
Aini became a pen
When did they finish making
this pen gecella was
09.10 10 seconds
he left the factory at that time
but I asked if leaving the
factory was Sisi  front Middle side
or Back side
This is a very sensitive idea
surely one side of this pen comes out
first right patrich maybe there is a
conveyor belt that no pull it out of the
factory Then slowly from the
front side out of the factory
for example 10 minutes after
9.14 seconds
then
appears The back side of this pen
comes out
50D 15th second but if so
when did the middle part come out Oh maybe
14 and a half seconds What about the
front half and the
back half gecella Who cares
listen you can't tell
me When is the exact time
in this pen comes out of this form because
Okay there is a party dots of time in
just one second that you can't
see just one second in
the end like this no it's beautiful hehehe
just one second there is a beginning and there is an
end time begins time ends
but there are more small parts
of time in this second right but
we can't see our minds
can't see it
for example today I want to
make a cake for my wife she
said she's not healthy but it's
okay My wife is sick I
want to make her happy
a cake will have several parts
right there is the top part the middle part there
bottom now listen ITB
if the parts are
too small for you to see if
you can't see the atoms of
the cake then you can't see the
whole cake if you ca
n't see the parts of the cake
then you can't see the cake
okay Guys I know I can't
see the atoms of a cake but
When you combine many atoms
into one we can see it right
you don't understand If the many atoms are
put together
Then you say Oh I can see
this is small but I can see But there
will still be atoms Here Nda
here and here there are also sides
corners of atoms too so if you
can't see the corners or
that then you can't see the cake
So the conclusion What is the conclusion
if you can't see this cake
then this cake is you can see me
here then I come from you time
also comes from you time doesn't
come to you but from you the atoms
of this pen don't come from
Vena to you but you this pen too
the atoms of this pen are too small for
you to see to you can't see
the ends because at the end there is
one
more atom  cdr.com If you can see the
tip of the pen Hi we view another
Chance Okay then The proof is this pen
comes from you not from the vein
itself If you
hope you have a
good life and you do good things
and after you die you will
get a good car that's
not how it works there is no
car there is no driver
only
your seed everything comes
from your seed no one
sees what comes from your seed
You are a
creature that comes from your
own seed you don't see what is strong
work or comes from your seed
You exist Hi what comes from
your seed don't feel you have a body
you have a house you have a
job you all come from seed
no one owns your body
no one has a new car no
one has a job you all
come from seed everything
in your life all cars all
colors all shapes all come from
your seed
and the people who see it also come
from your seed
no one else has that seed
Let's see the next sabaki
together yes
fortune Brother come on Jamet m.me answered
Than The Sun Story
girl d************ that the gods
they have children who are beautiful
and handsome
senson until  God they
are the children of the god
wender Bremen
Hyper Inn when the gods
saw
their children
Devi obese intense over them felt a
very strong attachment to
their children and they did not
realize
that these children came from
themselves
using my friends healthy Friends
live Hi my friend and Veronica just
gave birth to twins last week
Cut submit then
our Goat also had
two kids the same week ago
a. the mother of these two children was very happy
she
sent a photo of her two sons
who were being breastfed one on the
left one on the right She is very
happy
when you help and When you have a child
it feels like this child
came out of your womb and you feel
very proud
magical shop friend you feel a sense of
satisfaction
Oh I have given fun to eh
someone new and feel a
very strong attachment to
that person but what is being said here is
You do not see your own child
properly You do not understand
Where your children actually
come from your seed You keep trying
to lie so much the children come
from your seed and you create
yourself you know You create
your own pregnancy then you
create children who come out of
yourself and that's all  it comes from
your seed TV understand if you
understand where the origin of
ketupat really comes from you see them you will
want to be good to everyone So if
you haha ​​appears Who actually
created your child that is the
good seeds that are in your mind
then sometimes if we have
family members
eh
look like my siblings I don't know why
yeah Ah I see a lot of people
when they have children they
become better people
selfish people
worth brush these people become
better people
after having children because they
learn how to
sacrifice for others that is
their children when I was in the
diamond business I had to
employ
hundreds of people I had to find
them accept interviews they train
them then employ them for
19 years hundreds of people
and after a few years I
realized
drag workers in Montana Mothers are
very good workers
mothers are very good workers
If you want a good employee
Choose a mother because they know
how to sacrifice Kindergarten knows
how to get the job done
father will sleep when his child cries
but a mother will never so
I used to always
employ mothers because they know
how to sacrifice so sometimes the
form of arranging not you procedure Must
see someone who has children
they will become a person
better games more loving and
sometimes
in my observation because I
never had children 7 Habits of your copy
When you have children
kilesa You
Yogyakarta Angle you will have
too many attachments you become
more selfish you will defend and
love your own children more but you
do not care or love
other people's children because you think I
have to care for my own children
singing my own children but
my neighbor's children are not in not me Honey
tomorrow what I mean here there is a
misunderstanding
where your children come from
Andi this poem talks about the
children of the gods and know how the
gods have small children
that smell of tradition says that
children do not come out of the body of the gods
but one day Pop there is a child
in their lap suddenly appears
it feels This is a very
easy way to have children right
so the idea is like this
When You're Gone love you when a
child comes out of you there are also two
ways number one you can understand that a
very beautiful and precious brother
wants to come from you because we
share with others then after
you have children
and you still love ngerap Aa
other people's children mah know
if you do not understand Where
your child comes from
then the birth of a child  it could
be a bad thing
you only protect your own child
and don't care about other people's children
So if you understand that
your child was born from the seed of Genius then you
will understand
that your ceker implant you have to take care of
other people's children as well
okay now
Miss there is a very interesting dynamic
with the hungry gods
their whole life is
always filled with competition
or rivalry
Sangatta is similar to the type of ah
humans who are rich
I
listen to the radio at
night when I come home from
work while driving I need
45 minutes to drive I
live in the mountains I don't live
in the city I don't even have a
paved road When I drive
home  g at ​​night it's very beautiful
The scenery that I pass by
sometimes I listen to the radio
and I will
hear many things from other places
like from other states I
like to listen to the radio their radios
for example
from different places in
Hi kind of times people then I hear
famous people for example
movie actors yesterday I heard
an
interview they even talked
about other actors in the movie and
they called them as these are
my rivals and that's the way they think
these people who are very handsome
very beautiful very
famous men and women
I don't know why they you don't
have a big belly because of kofit
like me they always look
always beautiful and handsome but the more
beautiful you are physically and the more
famous you are
the habit that arises in you
is that you will become jealous of
others which is also this is like
a curse is a problem
of successful people rich people
beautiful people handsome people
they feel sometimes they
feel a very strong competition or rivalry
among themselves
or jealousy or envy or
with others and now they
panchen lama talking about these
people these gods have a
very beautiful life so
But one thing that defines
life  they the most important thing
in their life is envy it's
not enough that he's the number one actor
Word it's not enough that he won
awards they
look at other people Oh she's
prettier oh she's younger or Oh she's
stronger
Vans motif Oh she has a lot of fans
more people follow her
than me
this is talking about the science of
emotions on the
part of these gods they have
two emotions especially number one when
they have children
they feel a huge feeling of affection
towards their time
with then when they see
other Gods They feel a huge feeling of envy a
huge feeling of competition so panchen lama
said that bro closet let's think
about these gods Let's
think about these very beautiful
and handsome people who are so like this there
are two things that are the basis of their life
first they have their own children
and an incredibly strong attachment
to their own children
and a truly beautiful affection
for their children
but at the same time
They also have a huge feeling of envy
towards other beautiful people
other handsome people
so it's very strange that
these very successful beings
have a huge attachment to
their children
dh.com but at the same time also
feel a huge feeling of envy
towards other people  the
same as them and the old panchen is
not saying Oh you have to be a
good person, Yusuf
Oh you have to love others
as you
love your own child no
bias is not saying that is very
interesting what he is saying
is don't forget
this is a battle between the
devil and the Angel and the devil is saying
Oh look nutrition Michael instajool is playing
in your mind
there are two different thoughts number
one great
affection for
your students very good then number
great envy towards
other teachers for example
no he is not saying that no is not the
old panchen is not saying that
He is not saying Look
you have good thoughts and you
have bad
thoughts too and Please have more good
thoughts more and less bad thoughts no
He is not saying that he is
saying no one is having those
thoughts
no one is having those thoughts no one has affection
towards their children
competition and no one has
envy towards others that is the
devil speaking
if a Darma teacher says
no
ah increase your loving thoughts
and reduce your jealous thoughts
if a
Darma teacher says like that then
he doesn't know what he's
talking about because
when I tell you funny
you should have better thoughts
like the thoughts you have
towards your children edit or you
shouldn't have a&r thoughts
towards other people
then I'm talking about you
but Actually you don't exist if
you think that there is a pause
that has loving thoughts
towards your child If you
say that it is you who has jealousy
Then you have already
lost you are wrong Let's say it one
more time
shooting Usually if you say
that there is you who has loving thoughts and you say there is you who has
jealousy
and you feel you should have
more loving thoughts
and less competitive or
jealous thoughts then you have already lost the ground you
have listened to the devil because
there is no you there is no one who is
having those thoughts move Why are
we studying this If there is no
me to improve my ability
if there is no me
as once who will be
worse if I don't study then
that apple we
hold this class we don't but
there is no you only you seed there is no
you there is no one who gets out
of the old car gets into the new car
no one likes loving
their own children and hates
the success of others there is no you
only  The seeds that are opening
Only the seeds that are opening are
professional If there is no me
How can I be happy Who
becomes Buddha then Is there no one
who becomes Buddha no one who
becomes Buddha only young seeds that are
opening then you will become Buddha
on handphone
listen to someone the rise is open there is
no me Hi guys Nomi there is no
me who has happy thoughts or
unhappy thoughts you are you
those thoughts and you are your seeds
that are opening so don't worry
about me
worry about the seeds If you
see yourself
giving love to your children
you are seeing the seeds of
your love that are opening If you feel
competitive with others
you are only seeing the seeds of
competition that are opening that's all
So what should I do gecella
try to understand
you are seeing the seeds that are opening and
you have to focus on the seeds don't
focus on me hi okay just focus
on the seeds
yosela I have a problem Can't
meditate that I know even the seeds
that are opening there are seeing the
seeds that are opening the
last thing before we
continue with the Q&A I
have told this story several times
but grandpa has taught so many
classes I forgot what I taught
this is my kitchen yes You can see my kitchen
www.kentu.net
when I woke up  at night
and I
went into the kitchen to look for food
I always stepped in the water and every
night quietly
Hi I
stepped in the water
I was barefoot and I
felt the water was very cold because it was
winter here then I
felt I was responsible I
felt I believed this was a good person so
I had to wipe the water on the
floor then I knelt down
then I cleaned the water then I
thought Oh maybe I spilled water
or maybe the dishwasher leaked
then it's been 5/6 days 56 nights every
night I have to clean the water on the
floor then suddenly I don't know
what happened I felt I'm so tired of
cleaning the water website maybe
there's a leak in the pipe Come on we have to
fix the pipe it's all
very difficult to clean the
water every night maybe I have to find out where it comes from that's
what we're
learning here don't focus on the
results
okezone.com focus on the seeds
I called my friend Daniel Garcia
and he came he was there
he looked under the sink
and he
fixed the leak So what the
old panchen said here
is just think about your seeds
don't focus on the results
just pay attention to your seeds when you feel
in his love for you Then and when you
feel such great affection
there is your child and you  feel the
envy of your friends
are in your office looking at the
open seeds so just take care of
your seeds Don't think about me Don't
think about sliding Michael Jackson Michael
the feeling of affection comes out of the seeds and
envy also comes out of the seeds
and nutrition Michael Kelly Alvin
jealousy also comes from Islamiyah
seeds and sliding Michael gives
affection also comes out of the Pit so
Work for the seeds
find the pipe fix the pipe
the problem is
the person who is working for the seeds
get the seeds plant the seeds
yes it comes from debit therefore
whatever seeds you have is
okay t2v Watch out Edward also makes you a
better seed planter or
plant worse seeds
No one
can control it what seeds
you have today maybe tomorrow the
same seeds will come out again
so the seeds create the same person
who is planting the seeds So if there is a
problem with this seed then there will be Mas
there is a problem with the other seeds
ages la how come it's like a vicious circle How
come it sounds like we
can't improve ourselves it's difficult eh
Hi but it's not impossible
as long as you understand that everything
comes from seeds you have hope
So if you forget about it then you
have no hope
focus on the seeds focus on the
seeds Okay
if you have bad seeds
because you come from  from bad seeds
then the next day How
can I improve myself to improve
my orange seeds if I myself
came from bad seeds it seems
impossible huh Oh no because
we can do small things file is
very lucky that
chili seeds can grow Holy
multiply You can
do just one small good thing
then there is hope
because the seeds will multiply
multiply
so today is a
practical step
believer If you want to have a
good rebirth
do small good things
just do small good things
I'm cooking soup yes it's not a
very good soup I'm not a good
cook
Tibetan I'm better
than agar
but yes do good things like this
small good things to
others then we dedicate these seeds hey
we can dedicate to
pray ama able to resolve
international conflicts
do it like I cook this soup
I'll tell you tomorrow
Do I burn this soup or
not so just do small good things
plant the seeds then
these seeds will grow will get
bigger and let them grow That's
one of Our Hopes too okay
Timothy Do you have any questions
for me
I think we still have about 20
minutes
syakhson Thank you for teaching as Day
as light Thanks for this teaching nyari
Hehehe
description kenceng
This question continues from the discussion
about Hi pokespy seeds are not
my focus there are several questions that
come talking about seeds in
various schools for example in the main only
ngebibit stored in the key then
left wae higher we
say the seeds
are in the seeds themselves so
the question can you please explain
more about white Why are
we taught that the lips are stored
in us and now we press
say don't focus on me but focus on the
seeds that seem
outside me
interior school earlier in the lower school
it is said easy to say Be a kind person
grandma try how to plant good seeds
run safe in you will
get a new body grow sweet
that will be in a better place
and freestyle see that is the
first rotation of the wheel of Dharma and
taught to new people please
plant good seeds you will die you
want to have a
better rebirth so please Make
good seeds so you can
carry them like in a suitcase to the
next life with you can
open it there
what the
first speaker wants to say here is don't
forget
that the person who works with the seed
also comes from the seed at the same time
so the person who tries to
baek-hee the seed the presence of the person
who makes the new seed that is good that is
good at that time also comes from the
seed so the seed making seed is also
called also comes from the seed
itself So if you understand
there is a chance point but if
you think that it is a
seed maker that does not come from the lips at the
same time you will have a
problem there is a problem try
to understand
that the seed maker iso gawe also comes
from the seed for example
Mega's intention if the seed maker bootnya is
good today then the lip maker will
make good seeds n k
if the good seed maker is Mutia bad
today then the seed maker
will not produce good seeds
today So you have to understand
vestibule that the seed maker
also comes from the seed and we need to
plant the seed mega that will make
us become good seed makers
making titled seeds planting seeds also
comes from seeds so we have to
pay attention to
the small ones to plant the
right seeds to become a good seed maker
so we have to use a little
time to think about
Why I am
happy to plant seeds to Faisal Yap
understand must understand seeds Why
I believe in seeds
there are special seeds to believe in
lips and  it is the root of all
seeds
So what the first speaker said
is take care of the
seed maker think about Why are you
in the spirit to come to
class today there have planted seeds
before be
careful with the seeds take care of
the seeds And don't Lose the
seeds which means
giving pledge there is a keyboard keep
inviting others every time you
see someone doing something
good
tell them Wow that's cool what
you're doing
the whole thing about rejoicing and
coffee meditation and Hey give it
to others that's the
real seed stupidity to make you
become a good seed maker take
care of it
abya Ghana seed maker so the best way
News other people how cool they are
and that we do continuously but
don't lie
Don't make up stories You're
so cool but if the person is
poor don't say they're a
good person because this won't help
them I'm not saying that I'm
saying if you see something really
good
that someone else does and
tell them how cool it is
and that again guys
if you don't tell others
ask what they're doing
that's cool He is also a presenter when I
talk you see you talking
to a difficult person Rini You are so
cool I see how patient
ndhas I just  want to praise you I
wish I could be patient like that
more this seed to
encourage others
makes you a good seed planter
is so cool
so seeing other people
tell them how cool
their seed planting is Sarah honestly
when they are junub cool
it makes them a planter
held for this is what
digestion says increase where we
plant seeds
resistors taste name only school
research useful for just
finished his first book
green woodsmith this is he new with his book at
school play Oh he Basic taste Mother is
the coolest about mag school play
only ever translated
here the best book I've ever seen
about school play only
and
it comes out in a cartridge
called Perpres the book is called Golden
key golden key and if you really
want to understand about main only school play
only Take that book and chew on it
and ask word Smash
ask the website to teach you
about it
and this is so cool
I read a sentence recently
domain that is really amazing by
Jaejoong ship that is always right nit2
he said look at my review strange if
you really understand disco idea of
main only about their rezeki about me
lqas where you store GB and if
you delay  understand it then you can
practice Tantra
yantra Khan successfully You can learn the
secret teachings can live with
the angels if you really
understand it I'm like Wow that's really cool
and I really invite you
to study that book
too Islam I bought the book
gradation it directly we can
get it so cool with
your mother just order it and or
place it in
30 seconds Hi 30 seconds You don't have to
wait it will be posted we are quite
lucky because if we wait for the
post office maybe we need to wait 2
years to get the book
there can get the mother not less
than 1 minute
and iPad and many people tell
me
Oge taste school play that thing is
very difficult there are two things you can
do
the first is
if the book is not difficult it means you
already understand it and in my opinion there is
no reason to buy the book
And if the book is easy you will
already understand those things than In my
opinion and in In my opinion
and there is no need to buy the key to buy
the book and there is no reason for the
money if there is already understand something
Why should we buy the book in
my opinion and in the tradition of Congkak Sir
we have to buy books that we don't
understand our mission has to
take the book  that we don't understand
because then we can go deeper
and the
mixnut people they worked 56
years until now
everyone understands their
own book beautifully just shows
there is something
George Stephenson
Okay
here it is
we will show this week Dik
class MacBook You can see this
Hi
delicious yo you you can with the sweet home
there are come to class Semester can
read it these are the topics
nixstats can give you a
secret preview with unique news
fakhsirie but this is the source of all this
is the original Sutra
2,500 years ago
we translated
6 and the book
hisabi Tower this is Abdi Dharma
kitchen
yes also around
2006 ago
maybe
too Mahayana books
80800 years ago then looking uh
from Master asangga 17 centuries ago
then
dharmakirti
and the school of logic about how to think
no that
500 years ago
then the cool morality book Vinaya that 13
centuries ago
then the Tang Dynasty in China
cool translator who brought
this wisdom from India like the one that
tick then more strings
this is Sheila's camera
cool writer and they also like
meditation and they write books  cool
meditation about thirteen centuries
ago they wrote a cool book about
meditation after that Came ambe dawai
higher Chandra kirti
they really understood about
emptiness this amazing person
about thirteen centuries ago
eh e  h leak and lojong
how to develop a
good heart this came 10 centuries ago then
lamrim cool
days pretentious what about 600
years ago restart Then
study lessons about
different schools in two different ways to
study all the rubber schools
together
it is cool ideas from 2500 years
ago because there is something
interesting you see the
stairs dec The Second shrink this
Okay help Ragini are the books that
we Translate beside it we
stand out even six Sutra gay Cinema
Caca and people who do not
have many that have finished
the translation there can buy
various types of karmasuthra from light
lapis caramel ginger detailed review to
Sutra demen cutter then typical review
Sutra you can buy them all they
have finished
every great subject in ancient times has been
met by mixers
on the left and right you can see
Mike Smart Cover books and they
cover these cool topics
lately in
that Abdul the last thousand years are being
translated by mixmax
those mixpad books beside there are 27 translations
and if you do not
buy them the definitely crazy
So we Mike all and Nato
crazy people so if you  have time
this week we will have 60 classes on
these ideas you ask it's not
my fault you ask about
main only this face understand If you
want to Understand how the seeds are
in your mind come to the Cosmic
Smart class there are 27 different books that we are
stuck in Translate that
covers all of this okay one
more question can
invite ramenation question so it is a
combination question from several people
They ask about
teter
their partners it seems like they
don't love their family anymore and want to
leave
their family and there are people who also see
themselves as having lost their achievements
or someone else and can't
really feel that for anyone
else what Advice do you have for
dealing with
oxytocin that seems different but
people who lose Compassion
for others As you wish the question
This is the saddest thing in the world
on one side Indonesia you are
contacted have a relationship
and it seems the other side is losing
a bit want Well so or not
your love But before and this is very
disturbing this transfer like
water passing through your hand feels very
unique you can feel it is
happening see what is happening and it is a
very sad thing
you have feelings this person also has
feelings and now it seems like
the feelings are lost on the other side
and sometimes I am a person  who
lost the feeling
and I used to really care about
these people my family and
my partner and my work
and I don't feel that anymore Come on
and side not in love with them but
edited so instead of love I
feel that obligation Okay I have to
share with them this is my family this is
my partner this is the company that
drives pays me for years
I don't have a high up this feeling
Their radar spirit is no longer felt
It feels like wings ah their debt
both of them the feeling is not good by
me I
owe love to family and it's
uncomfortable
and see someone in my family and
in my company they don't
seem to
have the passion or around
like before and these two feelings are the
same team
it feels the same Abing the love is gone
and it's no longer there what we
can do energy
Hi
and
luckily the
first law of karma says
that small seeds can multiply
quickly and the first law of karma says
seeds multiply every 24 hours If
you understand seeds use
so it's cool Islam like that like
upox Super if you understand seeds and
the Land of a Million then the good seeds that you
plant will grow like very quickly very
quickly
If you see love lost that's the
cave like water on the floor by
trying to
pioneer the water  but fix the pipe
need
like it 4 water sources
so Sara personal
and wings My age is quite full I
see love lost often there is this
I think it is useless to
go to that person and say You
don't look like you already have love Please
improve yourself You have family
you have
our partner I to you try to have
more love and I can tell you it
doesn't work because it comes from
you
how much love they have
comes from you
you just have to do
[Music]
planting more love for the Prophet
of course love starts from appreciation
to others think about
beautiful people Hi serve you
Bridgestone
there are people who make planting
orange oral to be honest I there are people who
plant coffee seeds for my copy
can be there are people who plant
watermelon even in the winter
and so many people take care of me and
I have to show a little love
even just a little gratitude
so I I live in now
winter in Arizona It's so cold I'm in the
mountains and people send me
electricity Thank you
I don't know where it is but
if I pay
you this is what the Makassar account can
have electricity I can be warm on
cold days so try to have a
sense of gratitude for the beautiful things
in your life and that planting seeds
kates song Once that and this love  will
not be lost and the love will
return love is a big thing
sad love partner love family oh
my God we are yourself for
other people's families love for you
you can replant it you can
start that spark again by
showing gratitude to the
lengoh Thank you for making
my house warm thank you to the
coffee beans thank you to the internet
Thank you team for organizing
these classes and working like
ambiak all day all night
to give us all this opportunity
give your gratitude to
others and the love will return and Dini the
fun thing because when
working because this comes from a seed it's
so cool to know to
bring love back into your heart
or to someone else in your family
it's so cool
to be able to rekindle love
just from the moment His own side is
like fixing the pipe more
lips about being grateful
Kim ok